http://www.owens-pro.com/privacy_policy

Skip to main content
Select Vehicle
Year
Year202020192018201720162015201420132012201120102009200820072006200520042003200220012000199919981997199619951994199319921991199019891988198719861985198419831982198119801979197819771976197519741973
Make
Make
Model
Model
×
Jeep Products
Jeep Hood Vent
Jeep Fiberglass Hoods
Privacy Policy
Owens Products, Inc. operates http://owens.dotws.net/products. This page is to inform you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of the site.
We use your personal information only for providing and improving the site. By using the site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Owens Products, Inc. website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected on these pages are: name, address, email address, phone number.
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself or your company when placing an order, only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to view our complete catalog as well as receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to your account using your login and password. You will also need to contact us so we can be sure your account in our office system matches your online account. This can be done by sending an e-mail to Owens Products E-Mail or calling 269-651-2300. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Newsletters/Special offers
Users who sign up for e-mail newsletters or other services will occasionally receive information on news stories, products, services, special deals, etc. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.
Choice and Opt-Out
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the e-mail or e-mail us at Owens Products E-Mail.
Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 269-651-2300 or send us an email at Owens Products E-Mail.
TECH TIPSARTICLES TO HELP YOU GET MORE OUT OF THE PRODUCTS
Welcome to the Owens Family Matrix Jisko! May 15, 2019 We had the pleasure of meeting Matrix Jisko and his girl Ruby today. While on their way to Bluetick Days in Ohio, they made a stop to pick up their new Owens Dog Box.
We wish... READ MORE
Dealer Locator Update December 5, 2018 Calling all Owens Products Dealers!!! Now that our new website is up and running, we would like to work on our Dealer Locator list. If you are a Dealer of ours and would like to... READ MORE
Owens Products Sales October 11, 2018 We occasionally have overstock, close-out and scratch & dent items that we place in our eBay store at a discounted price. Please check back often to see what sales we may have... READ MORE
Your Jeep Deserves Owens Venum Jeep Products May 2, 2018
Owens continues to increase our Venum line of Jeep accessories and performance parts for the Jeep community. Our Jeep Venum Hoods are manufactured from dense layers of premium... READ MORE
ALL NEWS
OUR PROMISE TO YOU
MADE IN THE USADesigned & Manufactured in Sturgis, Michigan
At Owens Products, we produce many custom vacuum-formed plastic, fiberglass and aluminum products for a variety of companies. Owens Products has been a family-owned and operated company for more than 50 years. We strive to provide our customers with the highest quality products and superior customer service. We invite you to take a few moments to explore our world-class truck running boards, dog boxes, tool boxes, and more. Just one look and you will see why Owens Products is a world leader in aftermarket automotive manufacturing... and the best thing is, all products that Owens Products manufactures is Proudly Made in the USA!
Be sure to add the all NEW Extreme Weather Package to your dog box!
